const e=[{id:1,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"Layer Outlier",question:"Which device or service would not operate at the physical layer of the OSI Model",options:["Network Interface Card (NIC)","Router","IP Address","Cable"],random:!0,answer:"IP Address"},{id:2,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"Goodbye",question:"Which TCP flag is used to gracefully terminate a session between two systems",options:["PIN","FIZ","FIN","SYN","END","ACK","RST"],random:!0,answer:"FIN"},{id:3,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"What's the Point?",question:"Which statement correctly characterizes the functions of the OSI Model",options:["A method of describing the functions of a networking system to allow communication","A physical device used to connect computers to a network","A protocol used for encrypting network traffic","A type of network cable used in data centers"],random:!0,answer:"A method of describing the functions of a networking system to allow communication"},{id:4,type:"checkbox",title:"Presentation Powers",question:"Which common service(s) occur at the presentation layer of the OSI Model?",options:["encryption","compression","routing","IP addressing","packet switching","MAC addressing"],random:!0,answer:["encryption","compression"]},{id:6,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"",question:"Which device or service would not operate at the physical layer of the OSI Model?",options:["Network Interface Card","IP Address","Switch","Hub"],random:!0,answer:"IP Address"},{id:7,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"Communicate with who?",question:"Which type of communication would be analogous to a half duplex transmission",options:["a group chat where only one person can send a message at a time","two people using walkie-talkies","a one-way radio broadcast","two people talking on the phone at the same time"],random:!0,answer:"two people using walkie-talkies"},{id:9,type:"checkbox",title:"Guaranteed Delivery",question:"If you needed to be certain that your data transmission are being received, which type of connection(s) and/or protocol(s) should be used",options:["connection-oriented","TCP","connectionless","UDP","broadcast","multicast"],random:!0,answer:["connection-oriented","TCP"]},{id:10,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"I spy MTU size",question:"Which command can be used to determine the MTU optimal size?",options:["traceroute","ping","arp","ifconfig","hostname","nslookup","ipconfig"],random:!0,answer:"ping"},{id:11,type:"checkbox",title:"App Layer All-Stars",question:"Which protocol(s) operate at the application layer of the OSI Model",options:["SMTP","HTTP","FTP","TCP","UDP","SSH","ICMP","PIMP"],random:!0,answer:["SMTP","HTTP","FTP","SSH"],description:`**Correct**
- SMTP (simple mail transfer protocol)
- HTTP (hyper-text transfer protocol)
- FTP (file transfer protocol)
- SSH (secure-shell protocol)

**Incorrect**
- TCP (transmission control protocol): Transport layer
- UDP (user datagram protocol): Transport layer
- ICMP (internet control message protocol): Network layer
- PIMP (not a real protocol): if you fell for this you might not make it
`},{id:12,type:"checkbox",title:"Traffic cop",question:"Which type of traffic management service(s) occurs at the network layer of the OSI Model",options:["routing","error detection","flow control","segmentation","multiplexing"],random:!0,answer:["routing"],description:`**Correct**
- Routing: The network layer is responsible for determining the best path for data to travel across networks.

**Incorrect**
- Error detection: usually performed at the data link or transport layers.
- Flow control: transport layer (e.g., TCP)
- Segmentation: transport layer (breaking data into segments)
- Multiplexing:transport layer function (combining multiple signals)
`},{id:13,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"Who gets this?",question:"The TCP header specifies which value to ensure that data is processed by the correct application",options:["Port","Sequence Number","Window Size","Source IP Address","MAC Address","Protocol Number","Checksum","TTL (Time To Live)"],random:!0,answer:"Port"},{id:15,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"Node-on-node action",question:"Which layer of the OSI model is responsible for node-to-node data delivery and framing",options:["Physical Layer","Data Link Layer","Network Layer","Transport Layer","Session Layer","Presentation Layer","Application Layer"],random:!0,answer:"Data Link Layer"},{id:16,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"Choose your weapon",question:"Which device or service operates at the Data Link Layer to manage node-to-node communication",options:["switch","router","hub","firewall","repeater","bridge","modem"],random:!0,answer:"switch"},{id:17,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"LLC purpose",question:"What is the purpose of the Logical Link Control (LLC) sub-layer in the Data Link Layer",options:["It defines the physical addressing method for nodes","It manages communication with the network layer protocols","It is responsible for error detection and correction","It converts data from bits into electrical signals"],random:!0,answer:"It manages communication with the network layer protocols"},{id:18,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"Physical layer magic",question:"What is a key distinction of the components at the physical layer of the OSI model",options:["They use software to process data","They involve encoding and signaling to transmit data","They define the routing paths for data across networks","They are responsible for application protocols like HTTP"],random:!0,answer:"They involve encoding and signaling to transmit data"},{id:19,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"Not mine",question:"Which of the following is **NOT** a responsibility of the Data Link Layer",options:["Adding physical addresses to data","Error detection and retransmission","Framing data for transmission","Routing data between different networks"],random:!0,answer:"Routing data between different networks",description:"The Data Link Layer focuses on node-to-node communication within the same network â€” things like adding physical addresses, framing, handling error detection and retransmission."},{id:20,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"Bits to circuit",question:"In the OSI model, which layer is responsible for transforming data from bits into electrical signals for transmission",options:["Physical Layer","Data Link Layer","Network Layer","Transport Layer","Session Layer","Presentation Layer","Application Layer"],random:!0,answer:"Physical Layer"},{id:21,type:"checkbox",title:"",question:"What type of equipment resides at the Physical Layer of the OSI model?",options:["router","hub","switch","network cabling","repeater"],random:!0,answer:["hub","network cabling","repeater"]},{id:22,type:"checkbox",title:"",question:"Which of these protocols reside at the Transport Layer?",options:["UDP","IP","HTTPS","ICMP","TCP","ARP"],random:!0,answer:["UDP","TCP"]},{id:23,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"",question:"Which refer to a unique, 48-bit identifier also known as physical network address?",options:["SSID","IP","GUID","MAC"],random:!0,answer:"MAC"},{id:24,type:"checkbox",title:"",question:"Which of the following reside(s) at the Data Link Layer?",options:["bridge","media converter","switch","hub","network adapter"],random:!0,answer:["bridge","switch","network adapter"]},{id:25,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"",question:"The protocol data unit at the Physical Layer is known as:",options:["segment","frame","bit","packet","datagram"],random:!0,answer:"bit"},{id:26,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"",question:"Which layer assumes the responsibility for opening, closing, and maintaining connections between applications?",options:["Physical Layer","Data Link Layer","Network Layer","Transport Layer","Session Layer","Presentation Layer","Application Layer"],random:!0,answer:"Session Layer"},{id:27,type:"checkbox",title:"",question:"Which of the protocols listed reside at the Network Layer of the OSI model?",options:["ICMP","SIP","IP","ARP","SNMP"],random:!0,answer:["ICMP","IP"]},{id:28,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"",question:"The Transport Layer's UDP protocol data unit is known as a:",options:["bit","frame","packet","segment","datagram"],random:!0,answer:"datagram"},{id:29,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"",question:"Data format translation, data compression, and data encryption/decryption take place at which layer?",options:["Physical Layer","Data Link Layer","Network Layer","Transport Layer","Session Layer","Presentation Layer","Application Layer"],random:!0,answer:"Presentation Layer"},{id:30,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"",question:"A NIC resides at which layer?",options:["Physical Layer","Data Link Layer","Network Layer","Transport Layer","Session Layer","Presentation Layer","Application Layer"],random:!0,answer:"Data Link Layer"},{id:31,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"",question:"Which of the following devices resides at the network layer?",options:["switch","repeater","bridge","router"],random:!0,answer:"router"},{id:32,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"",question:"The Data Link's protocol data unit is known as what?",options:["bit","frame","packet","segment","datagram"],random:!1,answer:"frame"},{id:33,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"",question:"Which layer enables direct interaction between the end-user and the network?",options:["Physical Layer","Data Link Layer","Network Layer","Transport Layer","Session Layer","Presentation Layer","Application Layer"],random:!0,answer:"Application Layer"},{id:34,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"",question:"The Network Layer protocol data unit is called what?",options:["bit","frame","packet","segment","datagram"],random:!0,answer:"packet"},{id:35,type:"radio",category:"networking",subcategory:"",title:"",question:"Which of the following answers refers to a common Data Link protocol?",options:["HTTP","IP","ARP","ICMP"],random:!0,answer:"ARP"}];export{e as default};
